https://www.tierrayfuego.com/security-privacy.html

Chatelet Subway
3" x 6"
Subway
1"x 6"
2" x 4.25"
2"x 6"
2"x 8"
3"x 6"
3"x 9"
Subway
1"x 6"
2"x 4.25"
2"x 6"
3"x 6"
By Size
In 1"x 1"
In 1"x 6"
In 2"x 2"
In 2"x 4.25"
In 2"x 6"
In 2"x 8"
In 3"x 3"
In 3"x 6"
In 4.25"x 4.25"
In 4"x 8"
In 6"x 6"
In 8"x 8"
In 12"x 12"
In 13"x 13"
In 16"x 16"
Privacy & Security
Tierra y Fuego Online values its customers and respects their privacy. We collect customer information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests, and promotions. Tierra y Fuego Online recognizes that it must maintain and use customer information responsibly. We do not sell or rent the information you provide to us online to third parties.
This policy describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, click here to contact Tierra y Fuego, call us at 1-619-710-8885, or write to us at
Tierra y Fuego, 8785 Dead Stick Rd, San Diego, CA 92154.
If our information practices change in the future, we will let you know by posting the policy changes on our Web site or by communicating directly with you. We will notify you of any such change before we use your information in a manner not previously disclosed in our privacy policy. You will have the opportunity at that time to opt out of any new use of your information.
What kind of information does Tierra y Fuego Online collect?
We collect information (such as your name, email address, mailing address, phone and credit card numbers), that you provide when you place an order.
How does Tierra y Fuego Online protect kids' privacy?
Like you, Tierra y Fuego Online is concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet. In accordance of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If we receive actual knowledge that a subscriber to Tierra y Fuego Online is under the age of 13, we will remove all personally identifiable information about that person from our files.
What are cookies? Does Tierra y Fuego Online use cookies on its site?
A cookie is a small data file that Web sites often store on your computer's hard drive when you visit their sites. A cookie may contain information (such as a unique user ID), that is used to track the pages of the sites you've visited. Cookies will not be used as you shop at tierrayfuego.com. Instead, your IP Address is referenced to process your order.
How does Tierra y Fuego Online make sure my order information is secure?
Protecting your order information is a priority for us. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your online order information.
To check the security of your connection, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then SSL is active and the server is secure. You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https."
Some versions of browsers and some firewalls don't permit communication through secure servers. In that case, you won't be able to connect to the server and therefore won't be able to place an order through an insecure connection. If you cannot access the secure server for any reason, please print our order form and place your order by phone at 1-619-710-8885.
What about links to other Web sites and services?
Tierra y Fuego Online may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These Web sites have their own policies regarding privacy, which you should review before visiting them. We have no responsibility for linked Web sites and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.
If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you can send an email to
Tierra y Fuego, call us at 1-619-710-8885 or write us at Tierra y Fuego, 8785 Dead Stick Rd, San Diego, CA 92154.
^top
